<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Florida's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Doug and Lona Leugers, a top Real Estate Agent in Florida, shares their own internal real estate agent training for free. Their Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 09:48:34 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 09:48:34 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Rockstar Mastermind: Maximizing ROI</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RV3mc7Oew9s?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the latest episode of our Real Estate Rockstar Mastermind, we talked about how to maximize ROI by creating the right team structure. &lt;strong&gt;Here’s an outline of the discussion, with timestamps so that you can skip to the part(s) that interest you most:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:55- A common question we get from team leaders about commission splits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:35- An example of mistakes team leaders can make with their splits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:30- How can you keep your team accountable and loyal with a 50/50 split?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12:30- An example of a tiered system for handling different commission splits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15:00- How we hold our team accountable in terms of lead generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21:20- How we track SOI leads in our system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;23:20- How we handle any team member turnover in the middle of a transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;30:00- Our commission splits for our buyer’s and seller’s agents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;39:20- The only type of lead where we don’t have a referral fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;40:45- Recommendations for how to pay your ISAs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;45:00- A few final thoughts on agent compensation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to all of our wonderful guests for joining us for this insightful mastermind. If you have any questions for us about anything we discussed in the video above, please feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 11:49:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-rockstar-mastermind-maximizing-roi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/real-estate-rockstar-mastermind-maximizing-roi.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Mastermind with Mike Blake and Kristin Bond from the Mike Blake Team</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/u3KbSNzoIO8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recently had the awesome opportunity to sit down with Mike Blake and Kristin Bond from Rochester, Michigan, to talk a little bit about their business, their team, and what they’ve got going on. &lt;strong&gt;Here’s an outline of our conversation, which you can watch in its entirety in the video above:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:00- An intro to The Blake Team’s market, their team, and their business stats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:00- The Blake Team’s goals for 2018 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11:00- How Mike take’s his team members motivations and uses them to help the team grow as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:15- The best lead generation sources for The Blake Team and their lead generation budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;19:00- How The Blake Team is able to hire one new agent each month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22:30- How Mike and Kristin keep their agents engaged and continuing in their education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;29:30- The key to The Blake Team’s success in the real estate business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;35:10- How Mike and Kristin catch their new agents up to speed with training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;39:20- The Blake Team’s “Lead Days” and how they’re structured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;47:30- How Mike takes part-time agents and helps them transition to full-time agents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;51:30- How The Blake Team provides exceptional customer service and value to their clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:00:15- How the little changes The Blake Team made to their business helped multiply their volume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:05:50- The Blake Team’s No. 1 secret to success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for us about The Blake Team, the real estate market, or the real estate business in general, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 12:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-mastermind-with-mike-blake-and-kristin-bond-from-the-mike-blake-team.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-mastermind-with-mike-blake-and-kristin-bond-from-the-mike-blake-team.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
