<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title> Real Estate Podcast with Doug and Lona Leugers</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Team Freedom - your professional  Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Doug and Lona Leugers</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2022-03-21 12:07:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Doug and Lona Leugers</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Lona@TeamFreedom.International</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the  Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Team Freedom - your professional  Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s Happening in the Housing Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-happening-in-the-housing-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate Blog</category>
        
        <author>Doug and Lona Leugers</author>
        <pubDate>2022-02-28 22:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Here’s what you need to know about our crazy housing market. 

Today I want to speak with you about what’s happening in our market. As we head further into the year, things are just getting crazier and crazier. What does it all mean for you? Let’s talk about it. 

With inflation rising, many people are worried about their finances. Fortunately, real estate is a great hedge against inflation. If you check out the chart at 0:22 in the video, you’ll see that home appreciation has outpaced inflation in nearly every decade since the 1970s. If you want to protect your wealth, putting it into housing is a safe bet. 

So what about home prices? The chart at 0:56 shows how much the experts think home prices will appreciate by 2026. Even the most pessimistic predictions say the average house will increase in value by 23.7%. Meanwhile, the optimists believe they could go up by 62.5%!

“ Even the most pessimistic predictions say the average house will appreciate 23.7% by 2026.”

These predictions corroborate the latest data from Fort Myers and Cape Coral. The median sales price has increased by 26% from last year, up to $413,500. Meanwhile, our supply is as low as ever. Our active inventory has decreased 31% from last year, and closed sales are down 10%. Our market is still hot, so if you’re looking to sell, you’re in luck.

Finally, what’s happening with interest rates? If you look at the chart at 2:22 in the video, you can see how interest rates are predicted to rise for the next four quarters. According to the National Association of Realtors, interest rates could be at 4% by the beginning of 2023. This means the affordability for buyers will decrease, and demand could fall as a result. Home prices will still increase, just not at the rate they are now. 

If you have any questions about this market update, please call or email me. I’d love to help!  
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s what you need to know about our crazy housing market. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s what you need to know about our crazy housing market. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Tips To Increase Conversion & Organize Your Database</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-tips-to-increase-conversion-organize-your-database.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Agent Training Blog</category>
        
        <author>Doug and Lona Leugers</author>
        <pubDate>2022-02-23 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2022/3+Tips+To+Increase+Conversion+%26+Organize+Your+Database.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today we’ll share our top three tips to help you maximize your CRM. 

Leads aren’t cheap- we spend lots of money on leads to convert them. So how do the top agents and teams in the country prioritize their database to ensure maximum conversion? Here are our top three tips:

1. Prioritize your leads by placing them in three categories:

Category one- Brand-new leads. Prioritize new leads in your database that you haven’t even attempted to reach out to yet. Ideally, you’d pick up the phone and call them as soon as they register on your website. That increases your chances of converting that lead. Remember that people often register on multiple websites, so if you don’t get them on the phone as soon as possible, other agents will be happy to do it for you.

Category two- Leads from the last 14 days. For these leads, contact them consistently and often. We have leads that have been in our database for years, and we still get conversions out of them because we never give up.

Category three- Leads that have logged into the database most recently. We hit these leads hard because leads are the hottest when they are currently looking at listings. Leads can sometimes disappear for months before logging back in; just make sure that when they do, you catch them ASAP.

“ After you’ve identified a lead’s three w’s, schedule a reminder to follow up with them every 30 days.”

2. Take great notes. If a co-worker were to win the lottery and never come back to work, you should be able to look at their lead notes in the CRM and pick up where they left off. There’s no sense in starting over with each lead and having the same conversations over again. Be sure to write down their ‘why,’ ‘when,’ and ‘what’ so that you or your team know what’s most important to that lead.

3. Follow up. Many people drop the ball when it comes to this, but there’s gold in the follow-up. After you’ve had a conversation with the lead and identified their three w’s, schedule a reminder to follow up with them every 30 days. Most of our leads are years out from buying or selling, but we don’t want them to forget about us in the meantime.

If you have any questions about today’s tips or anything else to do with maximizing your real estate business, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We’d love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2022/3+Tips+To+Increase+Conversion+%26+Organize+Your+Database.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2022/3+Tips+To+Increase+Conversion+%26+Organize+Your+Database.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today we’ll share our top three tips to help you maximize your CRM. </itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today we’ll share our top three tips to help you maximize your CRM. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How To Engage Your Database</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-engage-your-database.html</link>
        
          <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
          <category>Agent Training Blog</category>
        
        <author>Doug and Lona Leugers</author>
        <pubDate>2022-02-09 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2022/How+To+Engage+Your+Database.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here's how reaching out to your database will increase your business.

Today we’ll talk about how to engage your database and sphere of influence to get more business in 2022.

Getting referrals from your sphere of influence is huge because those are people that already know you, like you, and trust you. The difference between your sphere of influence and buyer or seller leads is that they’re registering on many different websites and are getting chased by other Realtors. You should have leads coming in from different sources, and you should be chasing them. Working your sphere of influence will help maximize your business in 2022.

We’ve put together an awesome script for you to use and engage your database periodically. It’s really simple—it’s not designed to ask your sphere of influence for referral business; instead, it lets them know that you’re thinking about them and that you care. Those two things tend to naturally spark conversations about real estate. 

“Getting referrals from your sphere of influence is huge.”

Here is the script:

1. Hi (Client Name), I was just thinking of you and wanted to check in. How are you? (and family)

2. How are things with your home? Do you need any referrals to contractors, handymen etc? Please don’t hesitate to reach out if you do.

3. When you get a moment, please let me know how you are doing.

We recommend that you use this script on Facebook Messenger so that you can see if they got your video and whether they watched it. Don’t worry if you don’t get a reply; the point is to just reach out and let them know you’re thinking of them. Do that periodically but consistently.

If you have any questions, visit our website, and don’t hesitate to reach out to us by phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2022/How+To+Engage+Your+Database.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2022/How+To+Engage+Your+Database.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here's how reaching out to your database will increase your business.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here's how reaching out to your database will increase your business.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Happy Holidays From Us</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/happy-holidays-from-us.html</link>
        
          <category>happy holidays</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate Blog</category>
        
        <author>Doug and Lona Leugers</author>
        <pubDate>2021-12-09 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Happy+Holidays+From+Us+(2).mp4</guid>
        <description>

From our team to your family, we want to wish you a happy holiday season

Happy holidays to you!

The holiday season has officially arrived. We hope you enjoy this wonderful time of year and make some fantastic memories.

We wanted to take a moment to thank you for your continued support. We love helping people make their real estate dreams come true, so thank you for working with us and supporting our business.

This may be a busy time of year, but we are always here to help you and answer any questions you may have. Give us a call or reply to this email; we’d love to help you.

In case we don’t hear from you until 2022, have a happy New Year!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Happy+Holidays+From+Us+(2).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Happy+Holidays+From+Us+(2).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>From our team to your family, we want to wish you a happy holiday season</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>From our team to your family, we want to wish you a happy holiday season</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/happy-thanksgiving.html</link>
        
          <category>holidays</category>
        
          <category>happy thanksgiving</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate Blog</category>
        
        <author>Doug and Lona Leugers</author>
        <pubDate>2021-11-14 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Happy+Thanksgiving!+(11).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Why is expressing gratitude so important?

Dear clients, friends, and colleagues,

The 2021 holiday season has officially begun! We hope you are as excited as we are.

We’d like to take a moment to express our gratitude to all of you this Thanksgiving. We have met some truly wonderful people, and we’re proud to have helped so many reach their real estate goals over the years.

We wouldn’t be where we are today without all of your support.

Enjoy your Thanksgiving dinner—that’s what we plan to do!

In the meantime, please don’t hesitate to reach out to us if you have any real estate questions. We would be happy to help you.

Happy Thanksgiving!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Happy+Thanksgiving!+(11).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Happy+Thanksgiving!+(11).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Why is expressing gratitude so important?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Why is expressing gratitude so important?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Picture Your Goals With Vision Boards</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/picture-your-goals-with-vision-boards.html</link>
        
          <category>Vision Board</category>
        
          <category>Agent Training Blog</category>
        
        <author>Doug and Lona Leugers</author>
        <pubDate>2021-11-02 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Picture+Your+Goals+With+Vision+Boards.mp4</guid>
        <description>

 Here’s why you should use vision boards to visualize your goals.

As we move through the last quarter of the year, now is the time to evaluate your book of business and ask what you did well on and where you could improve. You want to set your goals for next year and plan how you are going to meet them. If you don’t have a target, you don’t know what you’re aiming for. We wanted to share with you a powerful tool to help you visualize that target: vision boards.

Feel free to watch the full message above, or skip to topics that interest you using the timestamps provided below:

0:35 — Vision boards

1:23 — What makes vision boards so powerful?

2:26 — Take time to focus on your vision board every day

3:31 — How we use vision boards

4:12 — What you can put on your board

4:54 — Some books on this topic

5:18 — Wrapping up

We hope these practices help you meet all of your goals this next year. We want to be a resource for you too, so if you have any questions, feel free to give us a call.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Picture+Your+Goals+With+Vision+Boards.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Doug+Leugers/2021/Picture+Your+Goals+With+Vision+Boards.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle> Here’s why you should use vision boards to visualize your goals.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary> Here’s why you should use vision boards to visualize your goals.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Rockstar Mastermind: Maximizing ROI</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-rockstar-mastermind-maximizing-roi.html</link>
        
          <category>Agent Training Blog</category>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <author>Doug and Lona Leugers</author>
        <pubDate>2018-09-11 11:49:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Doug+Leugers/Real+Estate+Rockstar+Mastermind+-Maximizing+ROI+by+Creating+the+Right+Team+Structure.mp4</guid>
        <description>

On the latest episode of our Real Estate Rockstar Mastermind, we talked about how to maximize ROI by creating the right team structure. Here’s an outline of the discussion, with timestamps so that you can skip to the part(s) that interest you most:

0:55- A common question we get from team leaders about commission splits.

4:35- An example of mistakes team leaders can make with their splits.

7:30- How can you keep your team accountable and loyal with a 50/50 split?

12:30- An example of a tiered system for handling different commission splits.

15:00- How we hold our team accountable in terms of lead generation.

21:20- How we track SOI leads in our system.

23:20- How we handle any team member turnover in the middle of a transaction.

30:00- Our commission splits for our buyer’s and seller’s agents.

39:20- The only type of lead where we don’t have a referral fee.

40:45- Recommendations for how to pay your ISAs.

45:00- A few final thoughts on agent compensation.

Thanks to all of our wonderful guests for joining us for this insightful mastermind. If you have any questions for us about anything we discussed in the video above, please feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Doug+Leugers/Real+Estate+Rockstar+Mastermind+-Maximizing+ROI+by+Creating+the+Right+Team+Structure.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Doug+Leugers/Real+Estate+Rockstar+Mastermind+-Maximizing+ROI+by+Creating+the+Right+Team+Structure.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Agent compensation is an important topic for team leaders in this business. We dive into this topic in great detail.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Agent compensation is an important topic for team leaders in this business. We dive into this topic in great detail.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Mastermind with Mike Blake and Kristin Bond from the Mike Blake Team</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-mastermind-with-mike-blake-and-kristin-bond-from-the-mike-blake-team.html</link>
        
          <category>Agent Training Blog</category>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Doug and Lona Leugers</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-17 12:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Doug+Leugers/Southwest+Florida+Real+Estate-+Interview+With+Mike+Blake+and+Kristin.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We recently had the awesome opportunity to sit down with Mike Blake and Kristin Bond from Rochester, Michigan, to talk a little bit about their business, their team, and what they’ve got going on. Here’s an outline of our conversation, which you can watch in its entirety in the video above:

1:00- An intro to The Blake Team’s market, their team, and their business stats.

5:00- The Blake Team’s goals for 2018 and beyond.

11:00- How Mike take’s his team members motivations and uses them to help the team grow as a whole.

13:15- The best lead generation sources for The Blake Team and their lead generation budget.

19:00- How The Blake Team is able to hire one new agent each month.

22:30- How Mike and Kristin keep their agents engaged and continuing in their education.

29:30- The key to The Blake Team’s success in the real estate business.

35:10- How Mike and Kristin catch their new agents up to speed with training.

39:20- The Blake Team’s “Lead Days” and how they’re structured.

47:30- How Mike takes part-time agents and helps them transition to full-time agents.

51:30- How The Blake Team provides exceptional customer service and value to their clients.

1:00:15- How the little changes The Blake Team made to their business helped multiply their volume.

1:05:50- The Blake Team’s No. 1 secret to success.

If you have any questions for us about The Blake Team, the real estate market, or the real estate business in general, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Doug+Leugers/Southwest+Florida+Real+Estate-+Interview+With+Mike+Blake+and+Kristin.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Doug+Leugers/Southwest+Florida+Real+Estate-+Interview+With+Mike+Blake+and+Kristin.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We recently had the opportunity to speak with Mike and Kristin from The Blake Team in Rochester, Michigan. Here’s what they had to say.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Doug and Lona Leugers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We recently had the opportunity to speak with Mike and Kristin from The Blake Team in Rochester, Michigan. Here’s what they had to say.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Doug and Lona Leugers</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Doug and Lona Leugers</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Team Freedom - your professional  Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
